

PROFILE

I seek a challenging assignment in organization that will utilize my knowledge and experience. My aim to contribute to the objective of the organization and to grow with it. Having an experience in the field of competition I can be sure of my commitments towards the company which will Endeavour far most in achieving goals.

CONTACT

PHONE: 7067604406, 8359997211

LinkedIn-

https://www.linkedin.com/in/bhaw na-joshi-2660a7187

Email-

Bhawna.joshi11111@gmail.com

Twitter - @bhawnaj40765209

Certifications-

Green HR Sustainable Business

<u>Business Certificate of Achieveme</u> nt_hzhhuiy_Bhawna Joshi

Hirist.com

<u>C:\Users\Asus\Downloads\certificat</u> e.pdf

BHAWNA JOSHI

Technical Recruiter_ Human Resources Management

Summary -

Human Resources with 3 years of experience in recruiting and staffing, monitoring turnover and retention and company compliance. Desire to apply knowledge of the industry to assist your company in all HR related needs and strategies I have natural interest in human resources and finance and Currently I'm working as a Technical Recruiter

EDUCATION-

Post-Graduation_ MBA in HR and Finance 2019- 2021 - 80 %

Sanghvi Institute of Science and Management DAVV University

Graduation_ B.com Hons. 2016- 2019- 75%

Shri Vaishnav College of Commerce DAVV University

Higher Secondary_12th Commerce+ Math's 2015- 2016 - 83%

Sarafa Vidya Niketan MP Board

10th MP Board - 2013- 2014 - 78 %

Shri Vaishnav Kanya Vidyalaya Indore, Madhya Pradesh

Proficiency and Capability-

- End to End IT Recruitment
- Communication and openness
- Endurance, Patience and Empathy.
- Managing and Motivating Staff Remotely
- Good Knowledge of IT profiles.
- Positive attitude and Self-Management
- Strong networking and relationship-building skills
- Good Knowledge of ATS platform- Ceipal, Success factor and Procurewise etc.
- Negotiating skills
- Data-driven mentality
- Advisable and Appropriate knowledge of job portals- Naukri, Monster, indeed, Shine and LinkedIn.

WORK EXPERIENCE-

Sumeru Global Technologies Private Limited

Job Title- Technical Recruiter July 2021-Till Now

Successfully recruiting candidate for various permanent/full time, contract positions on various IT MNC'S Technologies)

- Managed up to 15 requisitions a week (full time and contracts)
- Finding active and passive candidates using proactive sourcing methods, high touch direct sourcing and networking to find top candidates for current and future openings. Uses cold calling, data base mining blogs, internet/web searches, LinkedIn, employee referrals to generate candidate leads.
- Presenting fully screened qualified candidates to hiring managers in a timely manner.
- Provides training and doing Mapping
- Recruited in all regions of the India and having exposure of Offshore Requirements.

Clients- EY (Ernst and Young) _ BIG 4, Capgemini, Genpact, Tech Mahindra and Trianz

Edunomics Tech Solutions

Job Title- HR Recruiter Feb 2020- July 2021

- Handle End to End Recruitment and payroll section.
- Taking first round of Interview Sourcing and Screening
- Provides training to HR interns and new comers.
- Maintain leave structure, maintain cx deployer and manage daily activities related to projects.
- Develop a marketing/recruiting strategy that includes:
- *The job requirements and skills needed for the position
- *Selection of Websites (LinkedIn, Monster, indeed, etc.)
- *To post ads for the available positions.

Head Recruitment Services

Job Title- HR Recruiter Jan 2019- Feb 2021

- Partnering with hiring managers to determine Client's needs for IT and Non-IT Profile.
- Screening resumes.

- Performing phone interviews with candidates.
- Administering appropriate company assessments.
- Coordinating interviews with the hiring managers
- Following up on the interview process status
- Maintaining relationships with both internal and external clients to ensure staffing goals are achieved
- Communicating employer information and benefits during screening process

Computer literacy: -

- Proficient with Microsoft Word, Excel and PowerPoint.
- Created a filing system using OneDrive for the entire data to organize online documents
- Hands on Experience with Outlook- aware about good no. of functions and activities.
- Certification in Computer and Peripheral Hardware (PMKVY)

PERSONAL DETAILS-

Father's Name- Mr. Dhirendra Joshi

Marital Status – Single

Birthday- January 17th 1999

Nationality-Indian

Languages- Hindi and English

Address- E 5 Raj Laxmi Real estate, Rangwasa Road, Indore MP. 453001